donkeymails.com 2012-10-31

# DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout

|   |  | 

|  | Latest News  
---  
Welcome to DonkeyMails.com! 

Donkeymails is launched at February 3th 2005. Now some years later we've reached our 600,000 Member! We want to thank all our advertisers and members for the great support to make this possible. Not a member yet [Join Now!](http://www.donkeymails.com/pages/confirm.php) start with earning and cashout at no-minimum!! If you are looking for advertising please visit our advertise page [Click here to visit the advertise page!!](http://www.donkeymails.com/pages/advertise.php).  

| Statistics July 2012  
---  
Total Members | 625,000+  
Total Payouts | 1,400,000+  

Donkeymails Favorites Must join!-> [Smart Media (paid)](http://edelweis.smartmediatechnologies.com/) | [HomePagepays (FREE)](http://edelweis.homepagepays.com/) | [Stiforp NR 1.!](http://edelweis.stiforptour.com/?SOURCE=07) | [Work from home!](http://edelweis.onebigpowerline.com/?SOURCE=07dkm2site)   

**Hello all donkeymails members,

Today we have a great website that is now in Pre Launch that you really had to join [FunkyShark click here to join](http://rewards.funkyshark.com/act/edelweis?cid=news). This website is now in Pre Launch and is free to join, with a great low cost upgraded membership that let you earn cash into 8 ways. We really expect a lot from this new website which partly become of their great owner (scott wacker) their pay plan, and the program itselfs. So if you not joined it yet this is really the time to get in and to start your promotions [FunkyShark click here to join](http://rewards.funkyshark.com/act/edelweis?cid=news).   
Sebas Broekhof owner Donkeymails.com 

**

**DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout Respects Your Privacy** **Information Collected** DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, address, and email address). DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout uses member contact information from the registration form to send the member information about our company and email advertisements. 

Members may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We collect personal off-line information for the sole purpose of paying members for earnings from our program. This site contains links to other sites. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout uses a sign-up form for new members and advertisers. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address, address, and name). The member's contact information is used to get in touch with the member when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Public Forums:**

DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout, in the future, may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security:**

DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Children's Guidelines:**

We do not collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. We do not collect personally identifiable off-line contact information without prior parental consent. We do not distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information. We do not give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information. We do not entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.   

**Choice/Opt-Out:  
** DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Log in to your account and click the "User Account Info." Link. At the bottom of the page you will find the option to "Cancel Account". You may also [Contact Us](http://www.donkeymails.com/pages/contact.php) and request your membership to be canceled at anytime.   
  
**Correct/Update:  
**

DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Members Area - login and change your personal information. Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with DonkeyMails.com: No Minimum Payout, you can [Contact Us](http://www.donkeymails.com/pages/contact.php). 

**Our Favorite Traffic Exchanges - > ** [VastHits](http://vasthits.com/?r=66177)EARN CASH* ,[ Surfers2U](http://www.surfers2u.com/?rid=4987)EARN CASH* , [BigBeachHits 2 Ref Levels!New*](http://bigbeachhits.com/?rid=3163), [HitsClub Cash SurfNew*](http://www.hitsclub.com/?r=68386),[Hits-A-Million](http://hits-a-million.com/?refid=17242)NEW*+CashSurf! , [TrafficDelivers](http://trafficdelivers.com/?rid=63056)NEW* , [ListSurfing!](http://www.listsurfing.com/?rid=15402)NEW* ,[$$Sweeva Amazing$$](http://www.sweeva.com/ref/edelweis) , [NewWaySurf](http://www.newwaysurf.com/index.php?refid=9478&campaign=favtraffic) , [HitTactic CashSurf!](http://www.hittactic.com/index.php?refid=edelweis) , [High-Hits](http://www.high-hits.com/?rid=7490) , [Easyhits4u. NR1](http://www.easyhits4u.com/?ref=edelweis), [HitBandit](http://www.hitbandit.com/?ref=edelweis&cnn=allsitefav), [SmileyTraffic](http://www.smileytraffic.com/?rid=72) ,[ Soaring4Traffic](http://www.soaring4traffic.com/?rid=10052) , [Hit2hit](http://hit2hit.com/?rid=7) (* New Added!!) 

**This site is part of the[multimoneygroup.com](http://www.multimoneygroup.com/)our sites are:**
